in this video we're talking all about
hypnosis and direct suggestion and
that's because this is the easiest way
to help people make changes with
hypnosis especially if you're a total
beginner right I'm Mike Mandel and I'm
Chris Thompson and we are Mike Mandel
hypnosis and we run the Mike Mandela
hypnosis Academy so
Mike let's start this off what the heck
is direct suggestion what do we mean by
that direct suggestion is using powerful
Punchy short suggestions or directions
that your subject's unconscious mind can
use to make change okay so here's what
we're going to cover in this video we're
going to teach you when to use direct
suggestions we're going to talk about
how to craft those direct suggestions
and then how to move Beyond direct
suggestions when you're ready so when do
you use direct suggestions well
obviously you're going to use this after
you hypnotize someone and deepen the
trance okay and a pro tip is when you're
hypnotizing a person this is not the
time to be giving them the direct
suggestions your eyes are closing your
eyelids are getting heavy if you want
them to do something while you're
hypnotizing them you just tell them to
do it close your eyes and instruction
not a suggestion right so you're going
to hypnotize the person first and then
you're going to give your suggestions
and your direction now how do you
structure these suggestions though this
is system into this all right so let's
talk about the first thing is we want
them to be stated in the positive right
which means you're always going to tell
them what will happen or what they are
going to do instead of what they aren't
going to do right so if we were to talk
about let's say smoking cessation you're
not going to Crave cigarettes anymore
what other stupidness you won't wake up
in the morning and think of smoking as
soon as you you know have breakfast or
you're not going to tell them what won't
happen tell them what will happen you're
not going to waste all that money yeah
you're gonna keep it positive the next
point is we want to keep them short
right sure we do the best suggestions
are 10 words or less keep them short
tight so they go right into the
unconscious mind and we want them to be
simple right so a suggestion that is
short often will be simple but I guess
we can combine those short and simple
and positives this isn't the time to say
oh and you're going to feel all those
wonderful Sensations that you drift
below that no no keep it simple and also
you want to repeat them in different
ways right now how do we repeat a
suggestion in different ways well we can
use the different visual dual auditory
kinesthetic systems we can refer to
different angles like looking back or
looking into the future right and you
can use the words that your client
actually gave you during your interview
right right if the person yes I want to
wake up with a ton of energy in the
morning you're going to say and when you
wake up in the morning you're going to
have a ton of energy why because that's
what they told you they want that's what
they told you they want give your client
what they want now let's do a couple of
examples let's start with um insomnia
okay a great way to frame insomnia
suggestions would be you'll fall asleep
easily at night you'll sleep soundly
through the night you'll wake up feeling
rested and alert your bed will feel
extremely comfortable and that's a whole
lot better than saying there's no reason
to lie awake all night staring at your
ceiling asking yourself why can't I fall
asleep right now what about something
like Fitness okay let's do some direct
suggestions for somebody who wants to
become more fit and work out more your
workouts will become a natural part of
your day you'll enjoy becoming fit with
short powerful workouts exercise will
become exciting and fun you'll feel
amazing after every workout when you
look in the mirror you'll remember you
love exercise that's fantastic it would
be a lot better than doing it in the
negative and saying things like you'll
stop thinking of yourself as a fat
bastard you won't obsess over pizza ice
cream and donuts all day long Donuts
love donuts don't eat them though all
right so your best suggestions like Mike
said 10 words or less we're going to
keep them short so let's talk about
what's next well this is really powerful
direct suggestion in hypnosis and you
can use direct suggestions in everything
in fact when we say you should right
right but you'll want to add more tools
to your hypnotic toolbox as well all
kinds of tools can be added to direct
suggestion you can bolt them on things
like working with timelines or NLP
interventions or guided imagery imagery
the control room metaphor there's all
kinds of things that you can do and when
you have the option what you can do is
think about the hypnotic trance as a
container and within that container you
can do all kinds of things one of those
things can be direct suggestion in
hypnosis and we always recommend at
least bolting not on after doing some
other stuff so if you want to learn more
about hypnosis check out our website
Mike mandelhypnosis.com you'll see a
link in the description under this video
and you can get started with us for free