A real nail-biter here at Mile High Stadium.
The broncos down by one, and 30
seconds left on the clock.
Come on, Broncos, you can do it.
And I'm joined in the broadcast booth
by the stars of ABC's latest reality
show, billionaire versus bear.
Let's review the easy-to-follow
rules of your show.
Each of you thought you were in a race
to plant the taco bell flag at the north pole.
What you didn't know is, the race was a chase,
spiced up by the presence of the betrayer.
Well, now, the bear has a surprise for you.
He's not really a bear, he's a tiger!
Ho! Lookie there!
Denver just won the ballgame!
Oh, the Broncos won?
Why didn't I bet on them like
professor pigskin told me to?
Who's professor pigskin?
He's a pig who can predict
football winners in advance!
How is that possible?
Because he's got something no gambler's ever had:
A system!
I've gotten the pamphlet four weeks in a row,
and every time, the pick-of-the-week
has been right on the money.
Ah... I get it.
Every week, they send out two
pamphlets, half picking
one team and half picking the other.
Eventually, there's a small group of people
who only receive the correct predictions
and think professor pigskin is always right.
That's when they ask for your money.
I have money!
Dad, it's a scam!
A scam?! Not according to Eddie F. From Tucson,
or football millionaire in Beloit, Michigan.
Look, all I'm saying is, you really
should think twice before...
Expiration date: 06/08.
Oh, professor pigskin told me
to bet on the Raiders, but they look awful!
And with 37 starting players
out with the flu, the Oakland Raiders
have turned to drunks conscripted from local bars.
Spare some change, football dude?
Now, you have a good day.
Dad, how much money did you bet?
Hey, I didn't bet any of our money.
I just borrowed some from him.
Don't worry, we can hammer out a payment plan.
It's not my fault the Raiders lost!
It's professor pigskin's!
If he mentions that pig again, use two hammers.
But the pig...
Now, i do have a way we could settle this debt.
We would like to use your home
to shoot an adult film.
Yeah, it's called lemony lick-it:
A series of horny events.
Marge would kill me!
Please! There's got to be something else I can do.
Like mow your lawn every week for two weeks.
I can't do it next week.
All right!
You can shoot your gay adult film at my house.
I didn't say anything about gay.
I thought you guys were the gay mafia.
They're shooting an adult film at my house tomorrow.
How am I gonna get rid of marge and the kids?
Well, I got these free tickets to santa's village.
I know a guy who turns the dead
sleigh horses into jerky and sells it to bars.
Thanks, Moe!
Why would we want to go to santa's village?
It's august.
I want to see santa--
he can explain why he gave
me a playstation box
with nothing inside but a coloring book.
It got your hopes up, didn't it?
Homer, before I take the kids,
I want you to swear you're not up to something.
I swear.
And I'd also like to know why
your hand is in that cast.
Because you look even more beautiful
now than the day I married you.
Welcome to santa's village,
where it's christmas every day.
Closed on christmas.
Those reindeer look really uncomfortable.
That's because they don't
thrive in this environment!
Watcha reading, Santa?
Tom clancy's op-center.
You don't seem very jolly.
Well, santa got some bad medical news.
And... action!
We've been on this spaceship for a hundred years.
When will we ever get to planet satisfaction?
Hey, Homer, we..
Angela Dare!
Sultry Stevens !
Yeah, what is this, a reunion
of Fahrenheit 9 on 1?
Guys! Get out of here!
Homer, how'd you ever get Marge
to go along with this?
Look, if you promise never to tell her,
I'll let you be in the movie.
We just came over to borrow
a board game, but okay.
I've always dreamed of
working in an adult film.
I'll run the sound board!
And I'll perform in the sex scenes!
Merry christmas!
I'm your old pal frosty the snowman!
In your dreams.
Frosty!
Where's your magic top hat?
Oh, god, please don't tell mr. Roselli
I lost my hat again!
My christmas present to myself this year
was leaving that place early.
Mom...
I got a rash where the reindeer licked me.
When they put santa in the ambulance,
why'd they pull the blanket all
the way up over his head?
Now, look, I know this wasn't
the greatest outing,
but your father meant well, so
don't let him know that we didn't...
Are you guys almost done?
Listen, I got a tattoo of foghorn
leghorn on my right thigh.
Are we gonna get into any trademark
or copyright issues here?
'Cause we could put a band-aid on it
and say my character just got stabbed.
Relax, three guys'll put their hands on it, okay?
Now, everybody is very much in love.
And... action!
Homer! Is this a snuggle film?
You're in the wrong house, lady!
How could you allow this,
in the room where we do puzzles!
Honey, please, just listen
to what I have to say.
All right.
I owed the mafia money.
Where are you going?
Away from you.
When will you be back?
I don't know.
Who's going to watch the kids?
You are.
Me? But I'm the father!
Boy, Homer, I've never
see mom this mad.
Honey, come back!
You didn't say bye to the kids!
Bye, Bart.
I love you, Lisa.
Sleep tight, Maggie.
Today's the last day you can
eat the yogurt in the fridge.
Well, we better go eat that yogurt.
It's dinnertime.
Look, we've been down this road before.
I do something stupid you mom
leaves, we eat waffles.
We're out of waffles.
All we got is ketchup.
You mean Homer's famous marinara sauce?
No, I mean ketchup.
Where's your sense of magic and wonder?!
Come on, Marge.
When are you going to call?
Let it ring, play hard to get.
That's hard enough!
Oh, my darling, I love you!
Please forgive me!
Hey, Homer.
Moe, what are you calling me for?
You told me to call. You wanted
to see if your phone was working.
But what if marge tries to
call while I'm talking to you?
Ain't you got call waiting?
Of course, I have call waiting, you idiot!
I just never learned how to use it!
I might have broken the phone.
I better call Moe.
Hey, Homer.
Moe, will you get off the line?!
I guess I better tell them I'm coming home.
Marge, what a pleasant surprise.
I'm at a rest stop south of Springfield.
I know. You're sorry now.
Then you'll buy me some Quickie Mart Flowers,
maybe a box of candy, where half the pieces
mysteriously have testing bites,
and a week later you'll be back
to your old thoughtless self.
No, no, it's not going to
be like that, I swear.
Lemon cream.
You're going in the Marge pile.
I mean, I love you so much.
Yeah, I love you, too.
Hold on.
I'll be off in a minute.
Listen, buster, I had to buy
a club soda I didn't want
to get change for this phone.
An oogly-boogly!
Be still.
Don't give it the phone.
Settle down, sugar plum.
Look what daddy's got in his pocket.
Yummy, yummy kelp.
Good girl, yes, yes.
This animal means you no harm.
She's a sweet old Florida manatee,
also known as a sea cow or dugong.
Hello, Marge, where do we keep the
socks that don't smell like feet?
I'll call you back.
I'm Dr. Caleb Thorn, and I would do anything
to protect a manatee except
harm another manatee.
What if by harming a manatee
you could save two manatees?
But before you answer, consider this:
The manatee you have to harm is pregnant.
Those are the questions that
keep me up at night.
I see a manatee the needs a hug.
Hello, Marge?
Does the pizza guy take a check?
If so, where do we keep the checks?
And lastly, how do you write a check?
I think the worst part was when I realized
that homer lied to me.
From what you've told me,
it sounds like what your husband did
is nothing new.
Exactly.
I have a saying which goes,
"you can't teach a manatee any tricks."
Maybe you could just put a hat
on him and say it's a trick.
My point is Homer is the exact
same man you married,
and if there's a problem here, it's that
you keep expecting him to change.
He cares so much about those doggone dugongs.
I wish I felt that kind of passion.
Maybe I should join him on his mission.
Hey, lady blue, while you're sitting there
staring at the ceiling, you boyfriend's
in the parking lot with his hands in a walrus.
Yeah, that'll be good for business.
Got to find your mom.
Dad, I promise
I'll be good.
Can I get out of the dog carrier?
It was hard enough getting you in there.
I'm not letting you out.
Yeah, she came through here.
I believe she was looking to
rekindle her passion for life.
Ain't that right, victor?
Oh, yes.
Senora left for the coast
with a rugged, yet sensitive man of science.
Rugged? Is that the same as handsome?
Oh, no, no.
"Handsome" means he look at himself
in the mirror all day. "Rugged"
means you look at him.
Okay, water monsters, be friendly...
but not too friendly.
What do I do?
Talk to it!
Let it know you're not a threat.
Oh, okay. You know, up close
you're kinda cute.
You're a good thing.
I know it.
Let me clean out your ears.
I've bonded with him!
Where is he taking me?
To his underwater palace.
Just kidding.
It's a lagoon full of bugs.
Dad, I don't think we're
going to find mom today.
And I'm sick of eating
at restaurant chains
I've never even heard of like
Skobo's and Dim Willie'S.
Okay, kids, we'll stop for the day.
I have cousins near here.
We'll stay with them.
Country cousins?
Are they rubes?
'Cause I don't cotton to rubes.
The rubiest.
Look, a new restaurant chain.
Can we say it's my birthday
and get free stuff?
We'll say it's all our birthdays.
I cannot believe it.
Cousin Homer, how are you?
And this must be Bart and Lisa.
Well, aren't you nice-looking kids.
Hey, do you folks want to see a quilt
that's been in our family
for five generations?
I warned you he was an idiot.
Well, all I need is some
moonshine and someone playing
the harmonicky and I'm as
happy as a pig in plop.
We're having lasagna and caesar salad.
Don't laugh.
They're doing the best they can.
So, Homer, how are you?
Oh, just great.
Things couldn't be better.
And how is our lovely Marge?
She, was killed by a
falling air conditioner.
But that's terrible!
It wasn't all bad.
As part of the settlement, her
funeral was air conditioned.
Now if you'll excuse me, I have
to use the outhouse again.
Well, we don't have an outhouse.
My recording studio!
So how are we related again?
Our dogs are brothers.
Oh, yeah.
I see mom!
I've got my groove back!
We've got to tell dad!
Where is he?
You lost that first game to hustle me!
I can't believe how many
manatees we saved today.
And the ones we can't save,
we put to good use.
what am I supposed to do,
bury them at arlington?
Marge?
Homer?
These are for you.
Listen, I thought about what I did.
And it was really, really wrong.
I'm sorry.
Homie, I accept your apology.
I love you, Marge.
But I'm not coming back yet.
I've found a place where I'm needed.
You're needed at home!
And treated like I deserve.
I'm sorry, Homie.
I just can't find it in my
heart to come back right now.
Well, that's very reasonable.
You stole my wife!
I'll kill you!
Homer, I have no interest
in stealing your wife,
but Marge is getting something
from her work with me.
Something a strong, passionate
woman like her needs:
A purpose.
I can see why she loves you.
She doesn't love me.
She's just trying to find herself.
You know everything.
I don't know everything.
I'm just a man.
And what a man!
Okay, the key to this thing
is the manatees.
Is marge saving them or killing them?
Saving!
Okay. To save the manatees,
I guess I could donate
my time and money
and help build them a...
Screw that.
Dad!
Those jet skiers are headed
right for a herd of manatees!
Check out those gentle,
exotic sea creatures.
Let's whomp 'em!
Man, I just wish
we could see their tears.
why don't you pick on
someone your own size?
They are roughly our size.
In fact, they're bigger than us.
Look, if it were up to me,
I'd be harassing them with you.
If anything, I'd be the
guy who took it too far.
But I love my wife and
I want to win her back!
You're a brave man.
And we respect two things:
Bravery and tattoos that
look like barbed wire.
Let's go.
Rubes!
What did you call us?
Catch me if you can!
Manatees-- defend!
Attention jet skiers.
I have a court order here requiring
you to vacate these waters.
No court order's gonna tell me what to do.
Oh, man--
it's notarized!
Let's boogie!
Homer, are you okay?
How many fingers am I holding up?
Poor dumb country mouse.
Can't even count.
My sweet,
sweet Homie!
You sacrificed yourself for the manatees.
Rubes...
so many rubeS...
pounding me with their jet skis...
rubes.
Please, no, rubes.
I'm gonna take you home and fix you up,
'cause you're the real endangered species--
a devoted husband.
Marge, I'm always amazed you chose me.
And I always will.
I'm starting to think I should find a woman.
Yeah, miranda was nice, but I'm not driving
to corpus christi every time
she needs a light bulb changed.
Amen.
Hey, since we got the kids
with us, why don't we all take
a few days of much-needed r and r?
Don't you have to be back at work?
Yes.
But I've got a friend who
owes me a solid.
Smithers, who is this barrel-chested go-getter?
I believe it's a manatee
posing as homer simpson, sir.
Oh, that's cute.
I think this is the beginning
of a beautiful friendship.
Actually, sir, I believe he's
about to die of dehydration.
Good heavens!
Grab a sponge, man!
You might not ever get rich
but let me tell ya, it's
better than diggin' a ditch
there ain't no tellin'
who you might meet
a movie star or maybe
even an indian chief
workin' at the car wash...
...car wash
Transcript: Scarfo
Synchro: Toki & Ale